( Support Admin Watch on kissFlix.co )
[Genius Girlfriend]
[Episode 25]
Lin Zhixia?
Lin Zhixia.
♪ The narcissus rides the carp,
fading away in decay ♪
♪ Dark‑green lurks beneath the sea,
stirring the nebulae ♪
♪ Through countless nights,
you and I march onward ♪
♪ Probing, waking, and gathering
love gone mad ♪
♪ Say yes, and let the present reset ♪
♪ Our first night, my sunset ♪
♪ The whole world, just us two ♪
♪ Sleepless city, rising and falling ♪
♪ Breathing the faint hush of midnight ♪
♪ All around, someone strikes the fire ♪
♪ Lovers burn and wound one another ♪
[Electrocardiogram Report]
[Electroencephalogram Report]
I just feel a bit flustered
and can't sleep well.
Sometimes I feel my heart
beating really fast,
and...
I feel hot for no reason.
According to the report,
your blood indicators,
ECG, and EEG are all fine.
Are you under too much pressure
at work lately?
Not really.
Well then,
you can do a Holter monitor test first.
You have to wear this for 24 hours,
even when you sleep.
Then we'll see how it goes.
If that doesn't work,
we'll do a CT scan
of your heart and brain.
Is that necessary? It's so much trouble.
You have to take it seriously.
Your sleep quality really isn't great.
It's not serious, right?
It's not a big problem.
At around 7:30 last night,
what were you doing?
Your heart rate was a bit fast.
Yes.
Jiang Yubai chatted with me
for a bit after dinner.
Alright.
I know the reason now.
What is it?
It's just the changing of seasons.
Plus you're a bit nervous.
Just rest more
and don't overthink.
But I can't sleep.
Can you prescribe me some sleeping pills?
You can't take sleeping pills
for no good reason.
I'm reviewing your report out of goodwill.
You're not even
a patient of my department.
How can I prescribe them for you?
Are you sure I have no problems?
I'm sure.
Now off you go.
I need to do my rounds.
Shen Fuxuan insisted I'm not sick.
But I really feel unwell lately.
However, the checkup results
do show that nothing is wrong.
What do those straight guys know?
Tell me, where do you feel unwell?
When I interact with someone,
I get nervous for no reason.
I can't sleep well either.
Sometimes my heart beats so fast
that it feels like it's going to jump out.
Interact with someone?
Who? Jiang Yubai?
How do you know?
I think Shen Fuxuan is right.
You are not sick.
It's a kind of stress response.
A stress response?
It's like a problem
we often encounter during puberty.
We've had it before.
But everyone is different.
In puberty, there are early
and late bloomers,
just like in menopause.
Basically, your puberty is here now.
Then what should I do?
I have a folk prescription.
What is it?
A desensitization therapy.
We'll fight poison with poison.
Aren't you afraid of him getting close?
Then you should get close to him first.
Hug him, cuddle him, and hold his hand.
After enough exposure and attempts,
your body will naturally
become immune to it.
Will it work?
What's the principle behind it?
Don't ask.
Just try it.
Lin Zhixia.
Why do you suddenly want to play
a horror escape room?
I had some problems with my research.
So I came to find some answers.
You can find answers here?
I can look at the mechanisms and stuff.
My bad, my bad.
I forgot to consider
personal tolerance levels.
Should we continue
the desensitization then?
Of course.
If your experiment fails once,
would you just stop?
Besides, you did great this time.
We'll definitely succeed next time.
What's next then?
The cinema.
It's a bit hot in here.
Let's go out.
This movie isn't very good anyway.
Let's go.
I'm speechless.
I really am.
The way your brain is wired
is definitely different
from ordinary people.
Even a rock would get it by now.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's my problem.
My fault.
Don't blame yourself.
I really don't
quite understand this problem.
But if, like you said,
everyone goes through it,
then I'll accept it.
I can overcome it too.
You can do it.
Take your time to figure it out.
We asked you to come home
these past few days, but you didn't.
Your mother and I still want to have
a good talk with you.
Go ahead.
About you and Lin Zeqiu,
we don't approve of it.
Didn't you want me to date someone?
Lin Zeqiu is a good person
with a good job.
He got into a big tech company right after
graduation, and his salary is good too.
We've known each other since
childhood and know each other inside out.
What's there to disapprove of?
With your qualifications,
you could even find someone
better than Li Zhe.
Why Lin Zeqiu?
I don't get it.
I like him.
You like him?
In the grand scheme of your life,
liking something or not
is the least important consideration.
Baihui.
We really are doing this
for your own good.
When you were little,
we made you study hard
and not waste time and energy
on other things.
It was all so you could
get into Qingbei University
and lay a good foundation for your life.
You did it.
You stood on a starting line
that's different from others.
This proves that we were right.
Now,
we want you to find a better partner
so that your future life
will be free of worries.
Your dad and I
are pretty much set
in our ways for this life.
I don't want you to spend
the rest of your life
living like us,
feeling stifled.
But I don't think you two
are living a stifled life.
And I'm confident that,
with Lin Zeqiu's and my abilities,
we can live a good life
together in the future.
He works himself to the bone,
but he's just an employee.
He can make some money when he's young,
but his family background isn't strong
enough to weather any storms.
In the future, you'll have kids,
a mortgage, and car loans.
You'll face a lot of pressure
when you're middle-aged.
You don't see these problems now,
but that doesn't mean they won't appear.
How can we not worry?
But Li Zhe's family wouldn't
have this problem.
Even if your family encounters problems,
Li Zhe's family members are all local
and can provide a lot of help.
Tell me, you could have a life
with a house, a car,
and a nanny, but you choose not to.
What's the point of working
so hard every day?
But I don't care about those things.
I don't need a big house.
I don't need a nanny.
I just want to live a simple life
with the person I like in the future.
Jin Baihui, do you not understand
what I'm saying?
Your mother and I won't need you
to take care of us in the future.
But don't you know
the family situation
of that Lin guy?
Can he just ignore them?
You worked so hard to get into
Qingbei University,
just to find a family like this?
Baihui.
We really are doing this
for your own good.
I'm telling you, this is not a discussion.
Move back home immediately today.
We agreed to talk nicely.
Look at her.
She won't listen to anything right now.
Baihui.
You really need to listen.
I've listened long enough.
Please stop doing things for my own good.
I'm not moving.
I'll decide this for myself.
Ms. Zhou.
These are the new business collaborations
for Su Mo this week.
It seems his new drama has
brought him high popularity.
Even though there are no major brands,
the brand tone is quite good.
The positioning is quite smart.
Interesting.
Su Mo, why are you at the company?
Ms. Zhou, I came to deliver a contract.
Your momentum is pretty good lately.
Even though those
external collaborations are small,
you are making steady progress.
Thank you, Ms. Zhou.
It's all thanks to Tingting.
The company's resources are limited.
Sometimes,
following the right person is more
important than doing the right thing.
You're smart.
You should understand what I mean.
Su Mo.
Tingting.
What's wrong, Ms. Zhou?
Is there a problem with the contract?
It's nothing. I was praising you.
This newbie of yours has good taste.
What's wrong?
Did Ms. Zhou make things
difficult for you?
No.
I was just passing by.
So I had a chat with her.
About what?
Nothing.
Just a casual chat.
Don't worry.
I'll go deliver a contract first.
[Star Shine Media]
[Duan Qiyan]
[What are you doing?]
[Same place tonight.]
[Hey, reply if you see this.]
[Hey!]
[Are you going or not?]
[Are you there, Tang Tingting?]
I'm busy. Don't bother me.
[What are you doing?]
[Are you there, Tang Tingting?]
[What's wrong?]
[Are you angry?]
[I'll treat you to dinner. Don't be mad.]
Zhixia,
why the sudden call?
There's something I might need to
trouble you with.
It's no trouble. Just tell me.
I'll send you a paper in a bit.
Professor Lin,
I'm just a university undergraduate.
Would I even understand
the paper you send?
Did Tang Tingting ask you to mock me?
Of course not.
I want to apply for the
national project next month.
That's a good thing.
You can definitely do it.
But to apply,
I need recommendations from at least
2 doctoral supervisors in the field.
The professors in our school
with relevant expertise
have their recommendation spots
booked long ago.
So I wanted to ask you about
Professor Liu Qingsong in your
university's School of Mathematics,
the one who does
partial differential equations
and computational mathematics.
He's a leading figure
in our domestic field.
I wanted to ask if you know him.
Could you put in a good word for me
or introduce me?
I just want a chance
to show him our group's report.
I understand.
Prof Liu
is indeed the treasure of our school.
He supervised my major advisor back then,
so in terms of seniority,
he's actually my grand-master.
I can ask my advisor for you,
and let him give it a try.
But Prof Liu is very stubborn,
so I can't guarantee it will work.
It's fine. Don't feel pressured.
I'm just hoping for a chance
for him to see our project.
The project will speak for itself.
Okay.
How about this?
Tonight,
I'll ask my teacher to try.
I'll feel him out first.
Thank you, Duan.
Don't mention it. Wait for my news.
It crashed again?
[Cancel] [Post]
The computer died before I did.
My stomach is protesting.
My brain has gone on strike.
Help me.
Su Mo?
I saw on your Moments
that your computer broke.
I happened to be nearby.
So I bought some
late-night snacks for you.
Come on.
Eat over here.
Let me take a look at your computer.
Can you do it?
I'll try.
Gamers are all computer experts.
Alright, give it a try.
[Tang Tingting]
Being handsome is just one of
my Su Mo's many strengths.
Handsome?
How handsome can he be?
Tingting.
Ms. Zhou came to me today
because she wanted me to join her team.
I turned her down.
I know I made it to where I am today
because when I was at my lowest,
you didn't give up on me.
I know how much pressure
you've shouldered for me.
I didn't tell you then
because I was afraid of upsetting you
and making you think I didn't trust you.
I'm telling you now
because I think the credit
for fixing the computer
should make up
for me keeping things from you.
Tingting.
It's fixed.
Brat,
at least you have a conscience.
[School of Mathematical Sciences
Experimental Center, Qingbei University]
Engineer Xie,
please temporarily reduce
the resource quota for my project
by a quarter,
and give it to Dr. Lin's group.
Dr. Tan,
didn't you say before...
I know.
Just do as I said.
You can inform their group
about the new schedule.
Thank you.
Why are you here for no reason?
How harsh of you.
Can't I hang out with you for no reason?
Tang, calm down.
First, tell me why you're angry.
And where did this
inverse function come from?
Jiang,
I really don't understand
how I provoked Tang Tingting.
She hasn't talked to me for days.
I sent her so many messages,
and she only replied with a smile emoji.
What does that mean?
You're upset over that?
Don't you know her?
She's been violent since childhood.
I could handle physical violence,
but now she's learned
the silent treatment.
Isn't that more hurtful?
I'd rather she punched me.
Then I can only wish you strength.
What's wrong with girls?
They weren't like this in school.
Why is it that the older they get
and the longer we spend together,
the less I understand them?
Mr. Tao.
Qiyan.
About asking Professor Liu
to recommend the project
you mentioned earlier...
Yes, Mr. Tao.
How did it go?
This afternoon,
I went specifically to see him.
He rejected me before I could
even finish speaking.
You know his temper.
You'd better think of another way.
Okay, Mr. Tao.
Sorry for the trouble. I understand.
Okay.
How am I supposed to explain
this to Lin Zhixia?
Lin Zhixia?
What about her?
She asked me to help her with something.
She'd like Professor Liu to write her
a recommendation letter.
But you have no idea.
This old man is really difficult.
Getting a meeting with him
is harder than reaching the sky.
The Professor Liu you mentioned,
what's his name?
Liu Qingsong.
I see.
Send me Lin Zhixia's materials.
I'll handle it.
Do you know Professor Liu?
If you're talking about the little old man
from your school,
I do know him.
He's the most difficult client
I've ever met.
I have a speaker here
that I modified for him.
I happen to be delivering it
to him tomorrow.
Wow, what a coincidence.
It's a small world.
Okay.
I'll send you the materials
right now, Jiang.
You're the best.
[Runting] [Time-Customized Wedding]
[Inspiration] [Banquet Color]
[Chérie Atelier]
[About Style]
I'm home.
You're back.
Have you had dinner?
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Have a seat first.
Have I been
in your way lately?
What do you mean?
You...
Do you actually have a girlfriend?
Are you getting married?
I saw wedding brochures
on your desk.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to pry.
I just... happened to see them.
You saw them all?
Why didn't you tell me
that you were getting married?
What if she misunderstands?
Don't worry.
I'll pack up and move out tonight.
Sorry for bothering you
all this time.
Is this what you wanted to tell me?
Actually, it's my fault.
I originally wanted to
tell you after everything was settled.
Let me start over.
Jin Baihui,
I want to be your boyfriend.
The kind that leads to marriage.
Wait a minute.
Besides wedding planning,
I've looked at wedding dresses
and houses.
Let me tell you about it.
Because I didn't have much time,
I only found a few options.
But my savings
are enough to pay
the down payment for these.
Let me tell you from the beginning.
The first one...
It faces south and is well-ventilated.
And then there's this one.
The layout isn't as good,
but the lighting is better,
and it has a bright bathroom.
And this one.
The lighting isn't as good,
but the community facilities are better.
Which one do you prefer?
The layout isn't important.
Are they in a good school district?
We need to think about
schooling in the future.
School district... I'm looking for it.
This one.
This one is assigned
to the City Primary School
and City No. 1 High School.
And this one.
There are no schools nearby,
but there's a private kindergarten
in the community.
And this one. It's my favorite.
It offers direct promotion from
kindergarten to high school.
Which one do you think is better?
What about medical care?
Medical care
is the most important facility
for when we retire.
I have options for medical care too.
This one.
This one is a 15-minute walk
from a top-tier hospital.
This one has no hospital nearby,
but it's in a transportation hub.
A 20-minute taxi ride will get us there.
I've seen all these houses.
They're pretty good.
Pick one.
Pick one you like.
Actually, besides the houses,
I also...
♪ Only for this lingering warmth
of the moment ♪
Prepared a ring.
I know...
♪ Trading souls with the night ♪
The girl should choose the ring.
But I wasn't going to tell you,
♪ Every dusk I have stolen ♪
so I made the decision myself.
I picked one
that I think you'd like.
♪ Foretells a parting ♪
♪ Where did the storm start brewing ♪
If you don't like it, it's fine.
We can exchange it.
♪ Drenching you before we knew it? ♪
We can go buy one you like.
I'm fine with anything.
♪ Let me draw near to you ♪
♪ Let me imagine you ♪
♪ Let me sink into your ♪
♪ Scattered golden glow ♪
♪ Let the night blur your figure ♪
♪ Yet tear myself away from you ♪
♪ I can't fathom why ♪
♪ I've never truly possessed you ♪
♪ That blazing, radiant feeling ♪
♪ Once the rain stops, clouds disperse ♪
♪ Hence, time and again, I lose ♪
♪ Myself ♪
What's wrong?
Are you unhappy?
Nothing.
If you don't want to talk to me,
then I won't talk about Professor Liu.
Professor Liu?
Professor Liu Qingsong?
Yes.
I've already made an appointment with him.
At 9 a.m. tomorrow,
he will come visit you.
But since you don't want to talk to me...
Let's talk.
You...
How did you get an appointment with him?
Duan Qiyan said
he's very hard to talk to.
He will definitely come.
Tomorrow,
he'll visit your lab.
Get the materials ready in advance
and just explain it to him clearly.
I've communicated with him a few times.
I told him
a friend of mine
has a very interesting project
worth listening to.
You actually know him?
And you can communicate with him anytime?
You are amazing.
What else don't I know
about you?
It just means you don't know me
well enough.
Dr. Lin,
you have a tough battle tomorrow.
First of all, you
need to eat and sleep well.
Do you want some stir-fried beef?
Yes.
Let's go.
Tell me again what exactly happened.
[Hematology Department Ward]
What are you looking at?
You were so absorbed.
Are you nervous about
the experimental treatment?
It's normal for me to be nervous.
But you,
Dr. Shen,
you seem to be
in a really good mood lately.
Really?
It's probably because a patient recently
has been very cooperative
with the treatment.
She followed every piece
of medical advice meticulously.
It saved me a lot of worries.
Don't make it about me.
It's definitely not because of that.
Then it must be because...
Look at the weather outside.
It's going to rain soon.
On rainy days,
we can finally get a good rest.
How did you get to know Professor Liu?
You know what,
-the canteen's stir-fried beef was great.
-Forget about the stir-fried beef.
I'm talking about Professor Liu.
Professor Liu?
It's raining.
Let's take shelter.
It's raining so heavily.
Wait for me here.
I'll go back to the lab
to get an umbrella.
I'll be quick.
No need.
In such heavy rain,
we'll still get wet
even with an umbrella.
We might as well run back.
Let's go, Jiang Yubai!
Lin Zhixia!
Go change into dry clothes quickly
or you'll catch a cold.
What about you?
I'm fine.
Go change your clothes.
Let me dry your hair for you.
I... Um, I...
The rain stopped.
I... I'll get going now.
[Nano Eraser]
I only realized it later.
Every clumsy approach
and every seemingly unintentional touch
were romantic theorems hidden in formulas,
waiting for the final proof.
It seemed that
before we even confessed our love,
we had already rehearsed the feeling
of being in love a thousand times.